VALERII KOLESNIK

.NET C# DEVELOPER

My project history of around 3 years as .NET developer can say almost nothing comparing to other applicants. But my mindset is different. My purpose - bring high level solutions from the idea to the product or at least its part. Bring high level of dedication to my project flows. Conversant in a range of technologies - most notably .NET. My approach is methodical and creative. Production of readable code and project construction is my highest priority. Gained experience from my own projects hosted on github, successful projects completed on upwork and participation in university project development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2015 — Present Freelance

Upwork

WPF + ASP.NET developer

- Developed high-quality desktop application with WPF technology used for automatization Skype calls through Skype API.
- Created ASP.NET Web control for displaying the instagram and tweeter feed with required css-styles and required functional of pagination.

Nov 2013 — Sep 2015 Infrastructure Management System

ACTS Department, KPI WPF + ASP.NET developer

- Have fixed bugs, refactor the code, using best practices of MVVM.
- Developed visual element for ASP .NET application, which was used as prototype for further developments. Managed 3 interns for ASP .NET application development.

EDUCATION

Sep 2015 — Jun 2017 M.Sc., System engineering and automatization

National Technical University of Ukraine "KPI" Faculty of Informatics and Computer Technology

Sep 2011 — Jun 2015 B.Sc., System engineering and automatization

National Technical University of Ukraine "KPI" Faculty of Informatics and Computer Technology



CONTACT

Location: Kyiv

Email: klevalera@gmail.com

Phone: +38(097)83-22-027

GitHub: bit.ly/github-vk

SKILLS

C#
OOP & OOD
WPF/WCF

ASP .NET MVC

SQL
Web (HTML, CSS, JS)

Git